(Leonard:)Tonight's gonna be a good night
(Leonard:)And tonight's gonna be a good night
(Leonard:)And tonight's gonna be a good, good night
(Leonard:)Tonight's the night, uh, uh
Let's live it up, uh
l got my money
Let's spend it up...
(Sheldon(appearing in the back seat):)Good Lord.
Would you stop that caterwauling?
(Leonard:)What the hell are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Bleeding from my ears.
- What are you doing hiding back there?
- I'm sneaking into work.
(Sheldon:)Now, if the guard at the university
asks what's under the blanket...
(Sheldon:)...you tell him it's some lobster traps.
- Lobster traps?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)That's how Velma and Scooby smuggled
Shaggy into the old lighthouse.
(Leonard:)What are you gonna do
when you get to the university?
People are gonna recognize you.
(Sheldon:)Will they, Leonard?